[
  {
    "question": "According to legend, what happened on 1 August?",
    "answer": [
      "The oath on the R端tli meadow",
      "The Federal Council was founded.",
      "William Tell shot an apple off his son's head.",
      "Bern was elected capital of the country."
    ],
    "right": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "In which year was the R端tli Oath?",
    "answer": ["1219", "1281", "1291", "1305"],
    "right": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following four people was not present at the R端tli Oath?",
    "answer": [
      "Werner Stauffacher",
      "William Tell",
      "Walter Prince",
      "Arnold of Melchtal"
    ],
    "right": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Which were the three original cantons of Switzerland?",
    "answer": [
      "Uri, Schwyz and Bern",
      "Uri, Schwyz and Unterwalden",
      "Uri, Schwyz and Lucerne",
      "Uri, Obwalden and Nidwalden"
    ],
    "right": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "In which canton is the R端tli meadow located?",
    "answer": ["Uri", "Nidwalden", "Schwyz", "Lucerne"],
    "right": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Since when has 1 August been a Swiss bank holiday?",
    "answer": ["1291", "1612", "1848", "1891", "1899"],
    "right": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "Since when has the Swiss Psalm been the official national anthem of Switzerland?",
    "answer": ["1291", "1848", "1852", "1891", "1981"],
    "right": 5
  },
  {
    "question": "How many stanzas does the Swiss Psalm have?",
    "answer": ["2", "3", "4", "5", "6"],
    "right": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Which country also has its bank holiday on 1 August?",
    "answer": ["China", "Peru", "USA", "Nepal", "Benin"],
    "right": 5
  },
  {
    "question": "The Swiss flag is a special case because it is square-shaped. Which other country in the world has the same flag format?",
    "answer": ["Sudan", "Qatar", "Vatican", "Nepal", "Ghana"],
    "right": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "How many lakes does Switzerland have?",
    "answer": ["1,500", "2,500", "3,500", "4,500"],
    "right": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "How many mountains does Switzerland have that are higher than 4,000 meters?",
    "answer": ["43", "45", "48", "52"],
    "right": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "What percentage of Switzerland's total area is higher than 2,000 meters above sea level?",
    "answer": ["7%", "14%", "18%", "23%"],
    "right": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "END",
    "answer": [],
    "right": 0
  }
]
